it turns out that transform games with
原来，
imperfect information give rise to
信息不完善导致
subtly different classes of strategies
不同类别的策略
and in particular one can make a
特别是可以使
distinction between behavioral and mixed
行为与混合行为之间的区别
strategies and they're fundamentally
策略，从根本上讲
very simple to explain a mixed strategy
很简单地解释混合策略
is what is defined it completely
是什么完全定义了
stranded way we have a notion of a pure
搁浅的方式，我们有一个纯粹的概念
strategy that is what each agent needs
每个代理商都需要的策略
to do in all of their information sets
在他们所有的信息集中做
and a that is a unique action in each of
这是每个动作中唯一的动作
those information sets and a mixed
这些信息集和混合的
strategy simply a distribution over such
策略只是这样的分布
pure strategies a behavioral strategy is
行为策略是纯策略
subtly different
稍有不同
it says rather than start with pure
它说而不是从纯粹开始
strategies it simply says in each
它只是在每个策略中都说了一些策略
information set how should you should
信息集应该如何
you randomize it may seem like the same
你随机化它看起来像一样
thing but it really isn't and let's look
东西，但实际上不是，让我们来看看
at an example so take this take take
以一个例子为例
this tree and here's an example of a
这棵树，这是一个例子
behavioral strategy player one can do
行为策略玩家可以做到的
take action a with probability point
以概率点采取行动
five and G with probability point three
5和G以及概率点3
what does that mean that over here
那是什么意思
they'll randomize point five point five
他们会随机分配第五点，第五点
and over here the randomize point three
在这里，随机点三
point seven that's a behavioral strategy
第七点是一种行为策略
similarly a mixed strategy here would be
同样地，这里的混合策略是
something on the phone it says let's
电话上的东西说我们
look at two pure strategies for example
看两个纯策略
a G will be one pure strategy and B H B
G将是一种纯粹的策略，而BHB
H would be another fuel strategy and
H将是另一种燃料策略，
let's look at some convex combination
让我们看一些凸组合
some mixture of the two point six of the
两点六的某种混合
1 and point for the other that would be
1，然后指向另一个
a a mixed strategy now although they are
现在是一个混合策略，尽管它们是
defined quite differently one looking at
定义完全不同
the example might think that well one
这个例子可能认为很好
could really do the job of the other and
真的可以做另一个的工作，
in fact you'd be correct in this case in
实际上，在这种情况下，您是正确的
a very famous result paper by ku from
ku的非常著名的结果论文来自
1953 it was shown that in certainly all
1953年表明，在所有
these games of perfect information mixed
这些完美信息的游戏混合在一起
strategies and behavioral strategies can
策略和行为策略可以
emulate each other there is no this pair
互相模仿，没有这对
the equilibria in Mik strategies are
Mik策略中的均衡是
outcome equivalent to the equilibria in
结果等于
in behavioral strategies in fact it's
在行为策略中，实际上
not true only for games with perfect
仅适用于完美游戏
information it's true for games of
信息对
imperfect information that is games with
与游戏不完美的信息
information sets where agents don't have
代理商没有的信息集
full knowledge of where they are so long
知道他们这么久的地方
as those games have what's called
因为那些游戏有所谓的
perfect recall game of imperfect
不完美的完美召回游戏
information has perfect recall if
信息具有完美的回忆性
intuitively speaking the agents have
从直觉上讲，代理商有
full recollection of their experience in
充分回忆他们的经验
the game that means that wherever they
这意味着无论他们在哪里
are and each information set they know
是，他们知道的每个信息集
all the information sets they visited
他们访问的所有信息集
previously and all the actions they've
之前以及他们执行的所有操作
taken to see an example of a game
观看游戏示例
without perfect recall consider the
没有完美的回忆，请考虑
following game so player 1
以下游戏，因此玩家1
has here two nodes this node and this
这里有两个节点这个节点和这个
node and he cannot tell them apart
节点，他无法分辨
and you could think of it as basically
你可以认为它基本上是
sending two agents on your behalf to
代表您派遣两名特工到
play and neither the agents know which
玩，并且代理商都不知道哪个
of the two places it it landed in and
它降落的两个地方中的一个
particularly what the other agents agent
特别是其他代理商
did regardless of the interpretation
不管解释如何
it's the case that in a behavioral so so
在行为上是如此
first of all what are the pure
首先是什么纯
strategies in this case well the pure
在这种情况下的策略很好
strategies for agent one is simply L and
代理人的策略就是L和
one can in this information set either
一个可以在此信息中设置
do L or R so you either do L which means
做L或R，所以你要么做L这意味着
you'd go here depending where you were
你会根据你去的地方去这里
or do R and go here depending on where
或做R并根据位置去这里
you were this is for agent one and for
你是为了代理人而为
agent - there are again two pure
代理-再有两个纯
strategies so what would be a mixed
策略，这将是一个混合
strategy equilibrium in this in this
在这方面的战略均衡
game well that turns out to be fairly
很好的游戏结果
easy to analyze and we start with the
易于分析，我们从
observation that player two has a
观察第二个玩家有一个
dominant strategy play played play down
主导策略播放播放播放
and so no matter what the other player
所以不管其他玩家
does player two is is no worse off and
第二名球员的情况不会更糟吗？
in general better off by playing deep
一般来说，通过打深洞来更好
rather than you and so a best response
而不是你，所以是最好的回应
for player one to play to playing D is
玩家一到玩D是
playing R because they would get a
玩R，因为他们会得到一个
payoff of two rather than half of one if
如果不是，则得到两个而不是一半的收益
they played L and so LD is in fact a
他们打L，所以LD实际上是
equilibrium in this game
游戏平衡
notice the set of the ironic or
注意讽刺或
disconcerting fact that you have a very
令人不安的事实是你有一个非常
high payoff
高回报
that is actually not accessible under
在以下情况下实际上无法访问
mixed strategies and that will be a hint
混合策略，这将是一个提示
but what's going to happen with pure
但是纯粹会发生什么
strategy with behavioral strategies so
策略与行为策略
what would an equilibrium in behavioral
行为均衡会怎样
strategies look like here well to start
策略看起来像是从这里开始
with note that nothing has changed for
并注意到没有任何改变
player two they still have a dominant
玩家二他们仍然有统治力
strategy of D and let's assume that play
D的策略，让我们假设
that what about player 1 player 1 has
那玩家1玩家1有什么
the opportunity to randomize afresh
重新随机化的机会
every time they found themselves in this
每当他们发现自己在这个
information set so let's assume they
信息集，所以让我们假设他们
randomize somehow going left with
随机以某种方式向左走
probability P and writers' probability 1
概率P和作者的概率1
minus B what assuming prayer to play is
减B假设要玩的祷告是
d what is their expected payoff given
d他们的预期收益是多少
the parameter P well with probability
参数P井概率
with probability P times P they'll end
他们以P乘P的概率结束
up here and get a payoff of 1 so that's
在这里得到1的收益，所以
P squared times 1 with probability P
P乘以概率P的平方乘以1
times 1 minus B they'll end up here and
乘以1减去B，它们会在这里结束
get a path up 100 so that's a hundred
上到100
times P times 1 minus B with probability
乘以P乘以1减去B
1 minus P times 1 they will end up
1减去P乘以1，它们将最终结束
because this is a play one is not right
因为这是一场戏，这是不对的
a of 2 is not randomizing here with
2的a在这里没有随机化
probability 1 my speed they will end up
最终我的速度是1
here and get a payoff of 2 that's 2
在这里得到2的收益即2
times 1 minus P so this is their overall
乘以1减去P，这是它们的整体
payoff assuming the randomize P and we
假设随机化P的收益，我们
simplify it to this expression now we
现在将其简化为该表达式
simply look at the maximum here of this
只需看这里的最大值
quote this equation and the and the
引用这个方程式
maximum
最大值
is arrived at this value so with
达到这个值，所以
probability slightly less than half that
概率略小于
you left and slightly more than half
你走了，一半多一点
they go right that is player 1 and so we
他们走对了，就是玩家1，所以我们
end up with this equilibrium where that
最终达到平衡，
players that play one randomizer this
玩一个随机游戏的玩家
way and pair two plays down with
方式和一对二淡化
probability one so we see that the
概率一，所以我们看到
equilibrium with behavioral strategies
行为策略均衡
is when we have imperfect recall as we
当我们回忆不完美时
have here can be dramatically different
在这里可以有很大的不同
than the equilibria with mixed
比混合的均衡
strategies
策略